[{"answer": "Talking to my favorite person.", "docId": "120410pmt", "aSentId": 39, "question": "Can you quite believe you're in the green jacket on CNN, you know, talking to the world about being Masters champion?", "qSentId": 38}, {"answer": "No.", "docId": "120410pmt", "aSentId": 46, "question": "But can you believe it?", "qSentId": 45}, {"answer": "Yes.", "docId": "120410pmt", "aSentId": 70, "question": "And that someone needs to take control of George Zimmerman in particular very quickly?", "qSentId": 69}, {"answer": "We're encouraged, Piers.", "docId": "120410pmt", "aSentId": 79, "question": "But are you encouraged by Angela Corey's statement just now?", "qSentId": 78}, {"answer": "I really haven't viewed the Web site.", "docId": "120410pmt", "aSentId": 92, "question": "I mean how do you feel as Trayvon's mother seeing the man that killed your son, you know, thanking people over a Web site for the overwhelming support that he's receiving?", "qSentId": 91}, {"answer": "I think it'll be a sense of relief on both ends.", "docId": "120410pmt", "aSentId": 100, "question": "Not just for you and for the process of justice but also for George Zimmerman?", "qSentId": 99}, {"answer": "First and foremost, Piers, you have to understand the raising of Trayvon.", "docId": "120410pmt", "aSentId": 107, "question": "Everything that's been discussed and debated, is it possible, knowing your son better than anybody, is it possible that Trayvon could have instigated the altercation with George Zimmerman and could have been potentially doing something to him that could have provoked him into thinking my life is in danger?", "qSentId": 106}, {"answer": "Well, I was very upset and very disturbed as a criminal defense lawyer and as somebody who teaches professional responsibility to students.", "docId": "120410pmt", "aSentId": 138, "question": "What was your view as a lawyer of what went down today?", "qSentId": 137}, {"answer": "I don't know what may happen to his parents.", "docId": "120410pmt", "aSentId": 158, "question": "If there is no extension to the legal process?", "qSentId": 157}, {"answer": "I'd be surprised.", "docId": "120410pmt", "aSentId": 169, "question": "Given her statement today, given the way this story has been developing, you'd be pretty amazed, would you, if this didn't now lead to at least an arrest?", "qSentId": 168}, {"answer": ": Well, holding my head high.", "docId": "120410pmt", "aSentId": 210, "question": "John, we've had many a chat on this rock n' roll, rollercoaster ride, good times and bad times, how are you feeling tonight as his campaign manager?", "qSentId": 209}, {"answer": "Well, you know, look.", "docId": "120410pmt", "aSentId": 219, "question": "What was the moment for you guys when you realized the game albeit temporarily is up?", "qSentId": 218}, {"answer": "She is.", "docId": "120410pmt", "aSentId": 233, "question": "She's back at home now, right?", "qSentId": 232}, {"answer": "Well, absolutely.", "docId": "120410pmt", "aSentId": 243, "question": "Because presumably at some stage Rick Santorum having beaten Mitt Romney to a pulp with all he's got is going to have to turn around and say this guy should be president, right?", "qSentId": 242}, {"answer": "Well, look.", "docId": "120410pmt", "aSentId": 250, "question": "Does he hold out any aspiration of a potential VP slot or is that pie in the sky really, do you think?", "qSentId": 249}, {"answer": "Well, I think he's not going to look past November.", "docId": "120410pmt", "aSentId": 259, "question": "There's no reason given his age that he couldn't revisit this and campaign again next time around, right?", "qSentId": 258}, {"answer": "Yes.", "docId": "120410pmt", "aSentId": 286, "question": "Is this the end of the race?", "qSentId": 285}, {"answer": "They're not very significant.", "docId": "120410pmt", "aSentId": 300, "question": "I mean when we get to the next stage of primaries, how significant are they now in light of Santorum pulling out?", "qSentId": 299}, {"answer": "If you think it was tough and angry and vicious among the Republican candidates themselves, just wait, Piers, because this is going to be a brutal, a brutal seven months with hundreds of million of dollars spent on both sides.", "docId": "120410pmt", "aSentId": 311, "question": "Presumably they're already planning the mother of all negative assaults on Romney, aren't they?", "qSentId": 310}, {"answer": "I'm -- I watch the -- of course I'm not a huge player.", "docId": "120410pmt", "aSentId": 322, "question": "You a golf fan, Wolf?", "qSentId": 321}, {"answer": "Yes, go ahead.", "docId": "120410pmt", "aSentId": 343, "question": "Can I touch it?", "qSentId": 342}, {"answer": "Feels nice.", "docId": "120410pmt", "aSentId": 345, "question": "How does it feel?", "qSentId": 344}, {"answer": "It's overwhelming.", "docId": "120410pmt", "aSentId": 348, "question": "To be Bubba Watson right now?", "qSentId": 347}, {"answer": "Yes, for sure.", "docId": "120410pmt", "aSentId": 361, "question": "But it's genuinely why, isn't it?", "qSentId": 360}, {"answer": "Yes, it has.", "docId": "120410pmt", "aSentId": 372, "question": "It's been a quite extraordinary time for you, isn't it?", "qSentId": 371}, {"answer": "The TV show.", "docId": "120410pmt", "aSentId": 382, "question": "Why did you want that car so much?", "qSentId": 381}, {"answer": "No.", "docId": "120410pmt", "aSentId": 403, "question": "But can you believe it?", "qSentId": 402}, {"answer": "No, I think the six-inch putt to win was the big moment.", "docId": "120410pmt", "aSentId": 420, "question": "The difficulty of the shot and how it played out, was that the moment for you?", "qSentId": 419}, {"answer": "I trust everything in -- every ounce of my body, I trust it all.", "docId": "120410pmt", "aSentId": 440, "question": "What is it inside you that made you look down and say, I'm going for this?", "qSentId": 439}, {"answer": "ATSON: Right, exactly.", "docId": "120410pmt", "aSentId": 450, "question": "Other than don't conk it out?", "qSentId": 449}, {"answer": "I definitely wasn't thinking about this show.", "docId": "120410pmt", "aSentId": 461, "question": "Or is it all just focused on the shot?", "qSentId": 460}, {"answer": "You know, I -- like I've always said, it's just -- this is -- this is to honor my parents, to honor my late dad, honor my grandparents, honor all the people that have gotten to this point in my life, my friends, some of the golfers that stayed around, some of the family members that were there, all my fans on Twitter, Facebook, all my fans across the world.", "docId": "120410pmt", "aSentId": 465, "question": "You weren't think of me when you won the Masters?", "qSentId": 464}, {"answer": "The first thing that springs to mind is he told me I got two options.", "docId": "120410pmt", "aSentId": 497, "question": "How much of his son are you, do you think?", "qSentId": 496}, {"answer": "You know, I recognize that.", "docId": "120410pmt", "aSentId": 524, "question": "How did you become so composed in such a pressurized moment, if the rest of the time you're all over the place?", "qSentId": 523}, {"answer": "Well, I think you got to learn from every situation.", "docId": "120410pmt", "aSentId": 562, "question": "What lessons can you draw from that?", "qSentId": 561}, {"answer": "Yes.", "docId": "120410pmt", "aSentId": 576, "question": "Is he still the best you've seen, Tiger?", "qSentId": 575}, {"answer": "\"America's Got Talent.\"", "docId": "120410pmt", "aSentId": 596, "question": "Bubba Watson, what were you thinking?", "qSentId": 595}, {"answer": "Well --", "docId": "120410pmt", "aSentId": 602, "question": "What were you doing there?", "qSentId": 601}, {"answer": "Golf is boring.", "docId": "120410pmt", "aSentId": 604, "question": "What was the thought process?", "qSentId": 603}, {"answer": "I know who's not going to be a member.", "docId": "120410pmt", "aSentId": 648, "question": "What are they going to do?", "qSentId": 647}, {"answer": "You.", "docId": "120410pmt", "aSentId": 650, "question": "Who, me?", "qSentId": 649}, {"answer": "She said -- she didn't say much.", "docId": "120410pmt", "aSentId": 710, "question": "What did she say to you when you became Masters champion?", "qSentId": 709}, {"answer": "ORGAN: Yes, and --", "docId": "120410pmt", "aSentId": 717, "question": "When he's old enough to focus?", "qSentId": 716}, {"answer": "I did.", "docId": "120410pmt", "aSentId": 760, "question": "Did you make that yourself?", "qSentId": 759}, {"answer": "About nine feet.", "docId": "120410pmt", "aSentId": 767, "question": "I don't know, how far is that, about five feet?", "qSentId": 766}, {"answer": "Yes, it could be.", "docId": "120410pmt", "aSentId": 770, "question": "Oh, could be out of your range, couldn't it?", "qSentId": 769}, {"answer": "Don't you worry about me, mate.", "docId": "120410pmt", "aSentId": 780, "question": "What are you doing right now?", "qSentId": 779}]